

**A** 20 Via Lucca C116, Irvine, CA 92612

**M** 1 352 552 7216

**E** lindsay.codes@gmail.com

### **Summary**

I have experience working and leading cross functional teams in Design Research, UX & UI Design, and Front-End Development. I've owned projects, facilitated workshops, and consulted for teams at IBM, McGraw Hill, and Astral AR. I am currently taking on supplemental work to finance higher education.

#### **Education**

**Northcentral University** 2017-Present *School of Business*Master Degree in Business Administration

**Full Sail University** 2012-2015

Design and Development Degree Program

Bachelor of Science

3.8 GPA Average

6 Course Director Awards

#### **Professional Skills**

#### **UX/UI Design**

Adobe Creative Cloud Prototyping Tools (Axure, InVision, etc.) Design Research Multivariate (A/B) Testing

#### **Software Development**

HTML5, CSS3, SASS JavaScript, NodeJS, PHP, Python MySQL, MongoDB APIs (Consuming & Developing) Libraries & Frameworks React, Electron, Express, Laravel, etc.

Branding & Identity Digital Marketing

## **Work Experience**

**Astral AR, LLC** 2017-Present Director of User Experience

Responsible for the end-to-end user experience. Actively implements design strategies that cater to the needs of customers and stakeholders.

# **McGraw-Hill Education** 2017 *Lead User Experience Designer*

Collaborated on cross-functional teams to deliver a holistic experience for various educational applications.

**IBM Design** 2015-2017 Software Designer

Prototyped, collaborated, and consulted on multiple software products (including Bluemix). Gained experience in leadership, mentoring, and information architecture.

**Platinum Advisor Strategies** 2013-2014 *Graphic Designer* 

Designed and coordinated branding materials for Platinum clients. Customized and created website elements for client content management systems. Lead email marketing campaigns.

#### **Personal Skills**

Communication Ideation Collaboration Activation Commitment Dedication Brainstorming Innovation

<sup>\*</sup>I am a bit of a **Maverick**.;)